The young fight hard for justice.
Teen Titans: The Judas Contract is a science fiction,
animation, action film directed by Sam Liu.
Tara Markov is a girl who has power over earth and
stone; she is also more than she seems.
Is the newest Teen Titan an ally or a threat?
And what are the mercenary Deathstroke's plans for the Titans?
Damian Wayne / Robin (voice), played by Stuart Allan.
Jaime Reyes / Blue Beetle (voice), played by Jake T. Austin.
Rachel Roth / Raven (voice), played by Taissa Farmiga.
Terra (voice), played by Christina Ricci.
Garfield Logan / Beast Boy (voice), played by Brandon Soo Hoo.
Koriand'r / Starfire (voice), played by Kari Wahlgren.
Teen Titans: The Judas Contract is a 2017 American animated superhero film directed by Sam Liu from a
screenplay by Ernie Altbacker based on The Judas Contract storyline by Marv Wolfman and George Pérez.
It is the 29th film of the DC Universe Animated Original Movies, the ninth film of
the DC Animated Movie Universe and the sequel to Justice League vs.
Teen Titans (2016).
The film features the voices of Miguel Ferrer and Christina
Ricci as Deathstroke and Terra, respectively.
It was released three months after Ferrer's death in
January 2017 and is his final film role.
This film had its world premiere at WonderCon on March 31, 2017.
The film was released through digital download on April 4 and
through home media on April 18 by Warner Home Video.
Additionally, Crispin Freeman, Jason Spisak and Masasa Moyo reprise their respective roles from
Young Justice as Roy Harper / Speedy, Kid Flash, and Karen Beecher / Bumblebee.
The film explores themes of superhero, cartoon, based on comic,
superhero team, dc animated movie universe (dcamu).
The tone is thought_provoking.